Yes, it's true. There are extensive foreign ties,
and I think that would be a very valid step to take.
Good. I think so, too.
Yes.
Good. I think it's a good point.
Thank you.
On the shutdown, we are now about one week away
from military service members missing their paychecks.
We'll always take care of our military.
Would you encourage Congress to pass a standalone bill
to pay our service members?
Yeah, that probably will happen.
We don't have to worry about it yet.
That's a long time.
You know what one week is for me?
An eternity.
One week for me is a long time.
We'll take care of it.
Our military is always going to be taken care of.
Yeah, please, blue dress, blue.